{
    "subject": "resource/Anmol_Ghadi",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Anmol Ghadi (English title:Precious Time) is a 1946 Hindi film directed by Mehboob Khan, starring Surendra, Suraiya and Noor Jehan. The film was musical hit and still remembered for its music by Naushad, which have hits like, Aawaaz De Kahaan Hai, Jawaan Hai Mohabbat Haseen Hai Zamana and Mere Bachpan Ke Saathi Mujhe Bhool Na Jaana. The film also featured playback singer, Mohd. Rafi first notable song, Tera Khilauna Toota, and became the highest grossing film at the Indian Box Office in 1946. The film was remade in Telugu in 2001 as Manasantha Nuvve (2001), again in Hindi as Jeena Sirf Merre Liye (2002), in Kannada as Manasella Neene (2002), in Tamil as Thithikudhe (2003), and in Bengali as Moner Majhe Tumi (2003).",
    "human_readable": "Anmol Ghadi (also known as Precious Time) is a 1946 Hindi film directed by Mehboob Khan, starring Surendra, Suraiya, and Noor Jehan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9014753103256226,
            "question": "Who directed the film Anmol Ghadi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8628298044204712,
            "question": "What is another name for the film Anmol Ghadi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8430653214454651,
            "question": "What year was the film Anmol Ghadi released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7961930632591248,
            "question": "What language is the film Anmol Ghadi in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7692387700080872,
            "question": "What genre is the film Anmol Ghadi likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7619417905807495,
            "question": "What is the significance of the title 'Anmol Ghadi'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6987326741218567,
            "question": "Who are the main actors in Anmol Ghadi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6577483415603638,
            "question": "What might be a theme explored in the film Anmol Ghadi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5490302443504333,
            "question": "Do you know any famous songs from the film Anmol Ghadi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4943065643310547,
            "question": "Can you name any other films directed by Mehboob Khan?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Anmol Ghadi (also known as Precious Time) is a 1946 Hindi film directed by Mehboob Khan, starring Surendra, Suraiya, and Noor Jehan.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5816_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know any famous songs from the film Anmol Ghadi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5816_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What might be a theme explored in the film Anmol Ghadi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5816_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the main actors in Anmol Ghadi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5816_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5816_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5816_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5816_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5816_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5816_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5816_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5816_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5816_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5816_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5816_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided context information confirms that Anmol Ghadi (also known as Precious Time) is a 1946 Hindi film directed by Mehboob Khan and starring Surendra, Suraiya, and Noor Jehan."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}